Profile

I am a full stack developer with experience of a multitude of projects using PERN stack, as well as other libraries as frameworks such as jQuery, PHP, React/React Router and Redux. I have achieved all of this by using resources such as Codecademy and Udemy, while working full time as a registered nurse.

I am a successful and hard-working adult registered nurse; I have over a decade's experience in nursing. Progressing to Sister in charge, and then specialising in intensive care nursing.

I am a calm individual with a positive working attitude and have the self-discipline to learn new skill sets in my own time.

Recent Achievements

Completing Codecademy's Front End Engineer Career Path

Completing Udemy's Modern React and Redux course

Passing Immediate Life Support class

Purchased my first property at address shown above

Work Portfolio Project using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React/React Router, deployed with Netlify

Career History

Princess Alexandra Hospital - Emergency Assessment Unit (EAU) - 2010 - 2016

This was my first job post-graduation, I worked alongside many other multi-disciplinaries, enabling me to develop my communication skills.

It was a fast paced and high-pressure environment, in which I learnt to be organised and efficient.

I also completed a 6-month rotation in the Emergency Department, allowing me to increase my skill set.

I was promoted to Sister in charge, taking on further responsibilities such as managing each shift and being responsible for a team of junior nurses.

Princess Alexandra Hospital - Intensive Care Unit - 2016 to present

My current role requires me to provide specialist nursing care to my patients.

I have completed in house training to learn these new skills; however, it is an ever changing, on-going learning environment.

I have developed my communication skills further as it can be an intense environment requiring a certain skill set to communicate with patient's relatives.

Qualifications

University of Hertfordshire - 2007 - 2010

Diploma in Adult Nursing

Havering Sixth Form College - 2-5 - 2007

Travel and Tourism BTEC CertificatePass

GCSE - Emerson Park School - 2000 - 2005

Double Science	CC
English Literature	В
English Language	В
Mathematics	В